This cake is amazing!
这蛋糕太好吃了
My God,
天啊
get a room.
开房去吧
I would get a room with this cake.
开房好啊
I think I could show this cake a good time.
我一定会让这蛋糕好好爽爽
If you had to,
如果你必须放弃一样的话
what would you give up,
你会放弃哪一样儿
food or sex?
食物还是性爱
Sex.
性爱
Seriously,
说真的
answer faster.
你回答得也太快了吧
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
对不起  亲爱的
But when she said "sex,"
她刚才说的性爱
I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
我没想到是指和你一起的性爱
It's like a giant hug.
好象我还受了很大恩惠似的
Ross, how about you?
罗斯  你呢
Which would you give up?
你会放弃哪一样  性爱还是食物
Food.
食物
How about sex or dinosaurs?
那如果是性爱和恐龙呢
Oh, my God,
老天啊
it's like Sophie's Choice.
这简直就像《苏菲的选择》
Oh, God.
哦  天啊
What about you, Joe?
乔伊  你放弃什么
What would you give up, sex or food?
性爱还是食物
I don't know, it's too hard.
我不知道  这太难取舍了
No, you gotta pick one.
不行  你必须得选一个
Food. No, sex.
食物  不  性爱
Food. Sex. Food. Sex--
食物  性爱  食物  性爱…
I don't know! Oh, God, I want both!
我不知道  老天  我都想要
I want-- I want girls on bread!
我要坐在面包上的妞儿
《老友记》第十季第十集 钱德勒被"捉奸"
《老友记》  第十季  第10集 钱德勒被"捉奸"
You gotta see these pictures of Emma.
你看看艾玛这些新照片
Oh, how cute!
哇  真可爱啊
She looks just like a little doll.
她看上去就象个洋娃娃
Oh, no, that is a doll.
不不  那就是个洋娃娃
Oh, thank God,
噢  感谢上帝
because that thing's really creepy.
因为我觉得它看上去有点吓人
Look, there's Chandler.
钱德勒在那儿
Who's the blond?
噢  那个金发女郎是谁
She's pretty.
她很漂亮
He's having an affair.
他有外遇了
He is not having an affair!
他才不是有外遇呢
I'm always right about these things.
你知道的啦  我在这事儿上面感觉很准的
No, you're not.
不  你才没有呢
Last week, you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
上周你还在想罗斯想把你宰了
Well, sorry,
对不起
but it's hard to believe
但确实很让人难以相信
that anyone would tell a story that dull...
如果不是真的
...just to tell it.
谁会讲那么无聊的事
There's something going on with them.
我敢发誓他们俩之间肯定有些什么事
Look! He's getting into the car with her.
快看  他们俩上了同一部车
That doesn't mean anything.
那并不能说明什么
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
是吗  让我们走着瞧
Okay, duck down.
喂  趴低点
- Hello? - Hi, Chandler. It's Phoebe.
-喂  -嗨  钱德勒  我是菲比
I know that Monica is working today...
我知道今天莫尼卡要上班
...so I was wondering if you wanted to
所以我想你要不要
come to the movies with me and Rachel.
跟我和瑞秋一起去看电影
Oh, I have to work too.
噢  我也得上班
Yeah, I'm stuck here at the office all day.
我这一天在办公室也走不开
Well, it's a shame that you'll miss the movie...
太可惜了  你不能去看电影
...because we were gonna see, you know,
因为我们打算看
either Liar Liar...
《骗子  骗子》
...or Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
《出卖我的爱》或者是《不了情》
Those are all really old.
这些片子都够老啊
Okay, then maybe it'll be--
是啊  也可能会看
Dude, Where's My Car?
《老兄  我的车呢》
- What? - They're in a car.
-什么  -他们现在在车里
Okay. Well, talk to you later, okay? Bye.
好了  迟点再跟你说  再见
Okay, quick.
快
We gotta find a cab and follow them.
我们得拦辆出租车跟踪他们
Yeah, okay.
好的
Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
我得先去拿我的夜视镜和眩晕枪
I got them.
我这儿有
- Hey. - Hey. Hi, sweetie.
-嘿  -嗨  亲爱的
Hey, you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
你身上有香水和烟的味道
I was in the car with Nancy.
我今天和南茜在车里面呆了一天
Nancy doesn't smoke.
南茜可不抽烟
Well, at least the perfume's not mine.
香水不是我的
Be thankful for that.
你就应该谢天谢地了
So.... What did you think of the house?
那么  你认为那房子怎么样
It's everything we've been looking for.
简直太棒了  就是我们一直以来要找的
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wanes coating...
是吗  那些漂亮的方木涂层
...the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
拱形屋顶以及阁楼上的天窗
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps!
还有蠕虫和爬虫
What were the things you said?
你刚刚在说什么
Don't you love the huge yard?
你喜欢那个大院子吗
The fireplace in the bedroom.
还有睡房里的壁炉
And Nancy said it's really underpriced...
南茜还说这个价钱非常优惠
...because the guy lost his job
因为那家伙丢了工作
and has to move in with his parents!
不得不搬去跟父母住  所以急于出手
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
看把你兴奋的
So do you think we should get it?
你认为我们是不是应该把它买下来
I don't know. What do you think?
我不知道  你怎么想
I think we should.
我想我们应该买下来
I do too.
我也这么想
This is huge.
这是很大件事
How bad do you wanna smoke right now?
你有多想抽烟
I don't know what you mean,
我不知道你在说什么
giant, talking cigarette.
大只会说话的香烟
Phoebe called as I was getting
对了  我正在南茜车上的时候
into Nancy's car.
菲比打电话来了
If she asks you, I was at work all day.
如果她问起就说我一天都在工作
Got you. When do we tell them?
明白  你打算什么时候跟他们说这件事
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent.
先不告诉  没有十成的把握
Why upset everybody over nothing?
干嘛弄得大家都难受
Okay. Right.
嗯  好的
Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard.
天啊  这将非常难以开口
I know. Good luck with it.
我知道  所以祝你顺利吧
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
我就是不明白钱德勒为什么搞外遇
I'm telling you guys, we followed them
告诉你们吧  我们一直跟踪他们
out to a house in Westchester.
到一所位于韦斯特切斯特的房子的外面
They went in for 45 minutes,
他们在里面待了有45分钟
and then they came out looking pretty happy.
出来的时候两人看上去都很高兴
Chandler?
钱德勒
Forty-five minutes?
45分钟
Well, something's not right.
肯定有什么地方不对
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
我不敢相信他这样对莫尼卡
I know, and with the baby coming?
是啊  而且他们就快有小孩儿了
So should we tell her?
那我们该不该告诉莫尼卡
I don't know.
我不知道
Phoebe, if one of us saw Mike with another woman,
菲比  如果我们看到迈克跟另一个女人在一起
would you want us to tell you?
我们应不应该告诉你
Why? Who'd you see him with?
什么  你看到他跟谁在一起了
No one. I'm just saying if we did--
没有  我只是说
Tell me what you know!
告诉我你知道些什么
No one! Nothing!
没谁  没有
Mike's a great guy! It was hypothetical!
迈克是个好人  我只是在假设
All right. He is a good guy.
好了  他是个好人
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
你是对的  他不会搞外遇
If I did see him with someone,
如果我真看到他跟另一个女人在一起
there's no way l--
我也绝不会
Who did you see him with?
你看见他跟谁在一起了
Oh, look at her. So happy.
看看她  多开心啊
If only there were a smaller one
要是有更小的
to clean this one.
来清理这个该有多好
Hey, is Chandler here?
钱德勒在吗
No, he's picking up dinner.
不在  他去买饭了
Why? What's up?
怎么了  出什么事了吗
Look, whatever happens,
无论发生什么事
we're here for you, and we love you.
我们都跟你在一起  我们爱你
All right.
好
Chandler might be having an affair.
我想钱德勒可能有外遇了
What?
什么
Phoebe and I saw Chandler...
菲比和我今天
...with a blond woman today
在街上
outside on the street.
看见钱德勒和一个金发女郎在一起
And then we followed them
然后我们跟踪他们到了
to a house in Westchester.
一所位于韦斯特切斯特的房子
They went in together.
他们一起进去了
I'm so sorry.
很抱歉
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Oh, my God, that's awful.
我的天啊  这太糟糕了
What did you think of the house?
你们觉得那房子怎么样
What?
什么
Monica, you understand
莫尼卡  你明白
what we're saying, right?
我们刚才说的话  对不对
Yeah. Sure.
明白  当然明白
I mean, I'm devastated, obviously.
明显对我是毁灭性的打击
Did you think the neighborhood was homey?
你们觉得那附近住人舒服不
Hey.
嘿
You son of a bitch.
你这个狗杂种
Is it me,
只是我自己这么觉得
or have the greetings
还是我们打招呼的用语
gone downhill around here?
真的在走下坡路
Phoebe and Rachel saw you
菲比和瑞秋今天看见
with Nancy today.
你和南茜在一起
They think you're having an affair.
他们以为你和她有一腿
Who's Nancy?
谁是南茜
What's going on?
到底是怎么回事
Okay....
好的
All right, you better sit down.
好的  好的  伙计们  坐下说话
This is-- This is pretty big.
这是件大事
Yeah.
是的
I'm not having an affair.
我没有外遇
Nancy is our realtor.
南茜是我们的房地产经纪
I knew he couldn't be with a woman
我就知道他不可能
for 45 minutes!
跟一个女人做45分钟那么长
Why do you have a realtor?
你们为什么要请地产经纪
She's been showing us houses
最近以来她带着我们
outside of the city.
去看郊区的房子
What?
什么
Are you serious?
你是说真的
When we found out
当我们发现我们
that we were gonna get this baby...
马上就要有小孩儿了
...Chandler and I decided
我和钱德勒商量过了
we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
我们决定不能在市区抚养我们的小孩儿
So you're-- So you're gonna move?
所以你们要搬出去
Oh, my God.
我的天
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
这种事我们总要投票解决吧
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
在市区里带小孩儿有什么不妥吗
I'm doing it.
我就这样啊
Ross is doing it.
罗斯也这样
Sarah Jessica Parker:《欲望都市》女主角之一
莎拉·杰西卡·派克也是这么干的
And that's great for you guys,
对你们来说这没什么问题
but we want a lawn and a swing set.
但是我们想要给孩子一片草地和一个的秋千
A street where our kids
还有一条小孩
can ride their bikes...
可以在上面骑单车的马路
...and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.
不时还会有雪糕车经过
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
所以你们想买一栋50年代的房子
Have you thought about
你们有没有想过
what you're giving up?
你们正放弃什么
You can't move out of the city. What if--?
你们不能搬出市区  如果...
What if you want Chinese food at 5 a.m.?
如果你们想凌晨五点钟吃中餐怎么办
Or a fake Rolex
又或者想买一块
that breaks as soon as it rains?
一下雨就散架的假劳力士怎么办
Or an Asian hooker
又或者一个电话就能到的
sent right to your door?
亚洲应召女郎呢
You know what?
知道吗
If you want to look for a house, that's okay.
如果你们只是想看看房子  没问题
No! No, it's not! Don't listen to him.
不  不  不  别听他的
I'm gonna thump you.
小心我扁你
It's okay,
的确是没问题
because they have to get it out of their system.
因为他们必须得把想搬走的这心情发泄出来
Okay? But you're gonna realize
你们会发现
this is the only place you want to be.
这里才是你们真正想要住的地方
Actually...
实际上...
...we already found a house we love.
我们已经找到合我们心意的房子了
What?
什么
About an hour ago,
大约一小时以前
we made an offer.
我们开出了我们的价码
Bet you wish I was having
我想你们现在
an affair now, huh?
宁可我有外遇了吧
You put an offer on a house?
你们已经开出价码了
It's so sweet.
那房子真的很好
It really is.
的确是
It has this big yard
那里有一个很大的院子
that leads down to this stream.
一直通到一条小溪
And then there's these old maple trees.
那里还有很多老枫树
Oh, again with the nature.
跟自然环境有什么关系
What are you, beavers?
你们又不是海狸
Look, I know this is really hard,
我知道你们一时很难接受我们的决定
and we're really sorry.
我们也非常的抱歉
Is this because I come over here
是不是因为我常不敲门
without knocking and eat your food?
就过来拿你们的东西吃?
Because I can stop doing that.
我可以不那样做
I really, really think I can.
我真的可以改
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
乔伊  你知道这不是我们要搬出去住的原因
I think if you saw it,
我想如果你们到实地看一看的话
you'd understand.
你们会明白的
You guys were there.
你们俩去看过
It's beautiful, isn't it?
那的确很美  不是吗
Yeah, it is.
是  确实是很美
What the hell are you doing?
你在干什么
Well, it is, all right?
的确是  好吧
When we were out there today,
我们今天到那儿的时候
all I kept thinking was:
我所想的是
"l can't believe Chandler's
我简直不敢相信
screwing this woman...
钱德勒在和那女人干那事儿
...but, man, this would be a nice place to live!"
但是住这地方也太好了
Yeah, but so is this.
是  但住这也很好啊
Yeah. I mean,
对  我是说
if you move there,
如果你们搬到那里去住
you have to leave here.
你们就得离开这儿了
I mean, how can you leave this place?
你们怎么能离开这个地方
Come on, Daddy, listen!
老爸  你听我说
All my life, everyone's always told me,
从生下来  人们就跟我说
"You're a shoe!"
"你是一只鞋"
"You're a shoe!
"你是一只鞋
You're a shoe.
你是一只鞋
You're a shoe!"
你是一只鞋"
I stopped and said,
今天我停下来说
"What if I don't want to be a shoe?
"如果我不想当只鞋子会怎样
What if I want to be a purse?
如果我想做一个钱包
Or a hat?"
或是顶帽子"
I don't want you to buy me a hat, l--
不  我不是要你给我买顶帽子
I'm saying I am a ha-
我是说我是一顶…
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
我只是打个比方  老爸
You can see where he'd have trouble.
你知道他的问题在哪里了
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
好吧  也许我就跟莫尼卡住在这儿
I guess we've established
我想我们已经就谁
she's staying with Monica.
和莫尼卡住在一起这个问题达成了共识
Your money's mine, Greene.
你的钱马上归我啦  格林小姐
Your fly's open, Geller.
你的尿门没拉上  盖勒先生
You know what I just realized?
伙计们  知道我刚发现了什么吗
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J"!
Joker是带"J"的Poker
Coincidence?
巧合吧
That's "joincidence" with a "C"!
嗯  那是带"C"的"joincidence"
Look!
呃  看
Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
那个奇丑的裸男点了一堆蜡烛
That had to hurt!
那太疼了
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
嗨  这也是你们的感恩节
Instead of watching football,
除了看球赛
you could help.
你也可以过来帮我们干点活
We know.
我们会的
Rachel, you want to put the marshmallows
瑞秋  你得把这些果酱软糖
in concentric circles.
摆成一个同心圆
No, Mon.
不  莫尼卡
You want to put them in concentric circles.
是你想把它们摆成那样
I want to do this.
我只是想这样
Every year.
每年如是
It's stuck!
我被卡住了
Step.
别着急  小心阶梯
How did it get on?
你怎么会把头给套进去了
I put it on to scare Chandler.
我想把它戴上去吓吓钱德勒
Oh, my God!
我的天
Monica's going to totally freak out!
莫尼卡会被吓死的
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
还有  这里面难闻得要命
Of course it smells bad.
那是当然了
You have your head up a turkey's ass.
你脑袋伸到火鸡的屁股里面去了
Monica.
莫尼卡
Did you get the turkey--?
嗨  你们把火鸡...
Oh, my God!
啊  我的天
Who is that?
这是谁
It's Joey.
是乔伊
I got it!
有了
If we win,
如果我们赢
they have to get rid of the rooster.
你们就得把那公鸡拿走
That's interesting!
这主意好
If you win...
如果你们赢
...we give up the bird.
我们就放弃那只鸟儿
But if we win...
但是如果我们赢了
...we get your apartment.
我们要你们住的地方
- Deal! - What?
-一言为定  -什么
"What was Monica's nickname
莫妮卡在当曲棍球守门员时
when she was a hockey goalie?"
绰号是什么
- Big Fat Goalie. - Correct!
-大胖子守门员  -正确
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
瑞秋说她最喜欢的电影是
Dangerous Liaisons.
《孽恋焚情》
Correct, "Her actual favorite movie is...?"
正确  实际上她最喜欢的电影是
Weekend at Bernie's.
《老板渡假去》
"Monica categorizes her towels.
莫妮卡给她的毛巾分类
How many categories are there?"
一共分了多少类
- Everyday use. - Fancy.
-每天用的  -华丽的
- Guest. - Fancy guest.
-客人的  -华丽客用的
- Two seconds. - Eleven?
-还剩2秒  -11种
Eleven! Unbelievable! Eleven is correct.
11种  太不可思议了  11种是正确答案
"Chandler was how old
钱德勒第一次
when he first touched a girl's breast?"
摸女孩子胸部的时候有多大
- 14? - No, 19.
-14岁  -  不  19岁
Thanks, man.
谢了兄弟
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
乔伊有一个想象中的童年时的朋友
- His name was...?" - Maurice!
-他叫什么名字  -莫里斯
Correct! "His profession was...?"
正确  他是干什么的
Space cowboy!
太空牛仔
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
钱德勒·宾的工作是什么
Ten seconds.
还有10秒
You need this or you lose.
你们得答对这一题  否则就输了
Something to do with transponding.
嗯  好象是跟传送有关的
He's a transpons...transponster!
啊  啊  是搬运工
That's not even a word!
你说的都不是个单词
You are mean boys
你们这些讨厌的家伙
who are just being mean!
真是太讨厌啦
Don't get mad!
嗨  别冲我们发火
No one forced you to raise the stakes.
没人逼你越赌越大
That is not true! She forced me!
不对  是她逼我的
Hey, we would still be living here
要不是你答错了题
if you hadn't gotten the question wrong!
我们还住这呢
It was a stupid, unfair question!
那是一个愚蠢的  不公平的问题
Don't blame the questions!
不要把责任怪在题上
Stop yelling in our apartment!
你们能不能不要在屋子里瞎嚷嚷
You are ruining moving day for us.
你们把我们乔迁新居的日子给毁了
Chandler!
钱德勒
I saw what you were doing in the window!
钱德勒  我从窗户那里瞧见你们在干那事儿了
I saw what you're doing to my sister!
我看见你在对我妹子做什么
Get out here!
现在你给我滚出去
Listen, we had a good run.
哇  听着  我们的爱情长跑很长了
What was it? Four, five months?
有多久  四个月  五个月
I mean that's more
我的意思是这已经超过
than most people have in a lifetime.
大多数人一辈子的恩爱时光了
So, goodbye, take care, byebye.
再见了  自己保重  再见
Hey, Ross.
嘿  罗斯
What's up, bro?
出什么事了  老哥
What the hell are you doing?
你们到底在干什么
What's going on?
嘿  出什么事了
I think...I think Ross knows about me and Monica.
我想  我想罗斯知道我和莫尼卡的事
Dude, he's right there.
老兄  他在那呢
I thought you were my best friend!
我还当你是我最好的朋友呢
This is my sister!
她可是我亲妹子
My best friend and my sister!
我最好的朋友跟我妹子
I cannot believe this!
我简直不敢相信
We're not just messing around.
我们不是玩玩而已的
I love her.
我爱她
I'm in love with her.
我跟她坠入情网了
I'm so sorry
真不好意思
that you had to find out this way.
你是这样发现我们的恋情的
I'm sorry, but it's true.
抱歉  但这是真的
I love him too.
我也爱他
My best friend and my sister!
我最好的朋友和我妹妹
I cannot believe this!
我简直不敢相信
This is the last box of your clothes.
这是你最后一箱衣服
I'm just gonna label it
我会在上面贴个标签
"What were you thinking?"
写"你在想什么"
I was gonna go across the hall
有趣  因为我正想到对门去
and write that on Chandler.
在钱德勒身上也写上这句话
Guys, I don't mean to make things worse, but...
二位  我不想把事情搞砸
...l don't want to live with Rachel anymore.
但是我不想跟瑞秋住在一起了
-What? -What?
-什么  -什么
You're so mean to each other.
你们对对方太刻薄了
I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel.
我也不想像现在这样  弄得跟瑞秋不欢而散
I still like you.
我还是喜欢你
That's fine because I'm not moving.
菲比  那没关系  因为我不搬了
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
菲比  你得跟把她带走
You know, I know I said some bad stuff...
你知道  我是曾说过一些她的坏话
...but Rachel has qualities
但是  瑞秋还是有很多优点的
that make her a good roommate.
这足以让她成为一个好的室友
She gets tons of catalogs and she folds
她有很多商品目录
she folds down the pages of things she thinks I'd like.
她会把那些她认为我会喜欢的产品所在页折起来
What else?
还有呢
When I take a shower...
在我洗澡的时候
...she leaves me notes on the mirror.
她会在镜子上给我留言
I do. I do do that.
是  我确实这么干
That's nice.
很好
I like having things to read in the bathroom.
我喜欢在洗手间里有东西读
When I fall asleep on the couch...
当我看完书在沙发上睡着的时候
...she covers me with a blanket.
她会为我盖上毯子
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
你知道啦  我不想凉着你
And when I told her
还有  当我告诉她
that I was gonna move in with Chandler...
我要搬过去跟钱德勒一起住的时候
...she was really supportive.
她真的是很支持我
You were so great.
你太好了
You made it so easy.
你把一件困难的事情变得轻松简单
And now you have to leave.
但现在你却要走了
And I have to live with a boy!
而我得和男生住一起
- She really left. - I know.
-她真的走了  -我知道
- Thank you. - No problem, roomie.
-谢谢  -没问题  室友
- Can I ask you a question? - Sure.
-我能问你一个问题吗  -当然
What the hell is that dog doing here?
那只狗在那儿干什么
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
我来说点祝酒词吧
I know this isn't exactly
我知道这并不是
the kind of Thanksgiving you planned...
你们所计划的感恩节
...but for me this has been really great.
但对于我来说  这个节真的是太棒了
You know, I think because
知道吗  可能是因为这个节
it didn't involve divorce...
没有人离婚
...or projectile vomiting.
吐得一塌糊涂
Anyway, I think if
无论怎样  我只是在想
you had gone to Vail...
如果你们去了韦尔县
...or if you had been with your family,
如果你们和你们的家人在一起
or if you didn't have...
如果你"没有"
...syphilis and stuff...
梅毒什么的
...we wouldn't be all together.
我们就不可能在一起  对不对
So I guess what I'm trying to say is...
所以  我想我要说的是
...that I'm very thankful
我很感激你们
that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
因为你们的感恩节计划全砸了
- That's so sweet! - Thank you.
-太感人了  -谢啦
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
为糟糕的圣诞节干杯
And a crappy New Year!
也为糟糕的新年
Hear, hear!
此言极是
You can't move.
你们不能搬
You just-- You just can't.
你们就是不能这样做
Rachel's right.
瑞秋说得对
This is where you guys belong.
你们俩是属于这里的
Yeah.You don't wanna live in Westchester.
是啊  你们肯定不会想住到韦斯特切斯特
That's the worst of the Chesters.
感觉那是最糟糕的切斯特
You know,
知道吗
sometimes when I'm alone in my apartment,
有时我独自一人在我的寓所的时候
I look over here...
望向这边
...and you guys are just having dinner...
你们正在吃晚餐
...or watching TV or something...
看电视或是做着其它什么事
...but it makes me feel better.
这会让我感觉好很多
And now when I look over,
你们搬走后  我再望过来的时候
who am I gonna see?
我会看到谁
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
张三  李四  王二麻子
They don't make me feel so good.
他们不会让我感觉如此之好
Yeah. So don't move, okay?
是啊  所以别搬了
Just stay here...
对  就留下吧
...and maybe close your blinds at night.
晚上的时候别忘了拉窗帘就行了
Hey.
喂
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
是南茜  他们答复我们开出的价码了
And?
结果呢
Okay. Thanks.
好的  谢谢
They passed.
他们对我们的出价没兴趣
They said they won't go a penny under the asking price.
他们一个子儿也不愿少
- We can't afford that. - I know.
-我们负担不起那价格  -我知道
Well, there you go.
好了  如你们所愿了
I'm really sorry, you guys.
真抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry too.
我也很抱歉
I'm even more sorry that phone call didn't come...
要是那个电话在我说出从窗户那边望过来之前
...before I told you about looking through the window.
打来的话  就好了
Yeah. Well, we're gonna let you be alone.
我们还是让你们俩单独待一会儿吧
You gonna be okay?
你们没事吧
Yeah, we'll be okay.
我们没事的
Love you guys.
我爱你们
You know, I'm really sorry
刚才没有支持你们
I wasn't more supportive before.
很抱歉
That's okay.
没关系
We understand.
我们能理解
Yeah, and about this Nancy....
对了  关于这个南茜
If you're not sleeping with her, should l?
如果你没跟她上床的话  能不能让我上
I know there'll be other houses, but I just--
我知道外面还有很多房子  但是我...
- I love that one so much. - Yeah.
-我太爱这栋房子了  -  是啊
Well, it's a good thing we got it then.
所以得到这栋房子是天大的喜事
- What? - We got the house.
-什么  -我们买到那房子了
Oh, my God.
噢  我的天
I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
我只是不想当着他们的面告诉你
Oh my god, we got it?! We got the house?!
我的天啊  我们得到了  我们买到那栋房子了
We're getting a house!
我们买到那栋房子了
- We're getting a house. - And a baby.
-对  我们买房了  -还有小孩
We're growing up.
我们长大了
We sure are.
是啊
- Who's gonna tell them? - Not it!
-谁去跟他们说呢  -不是我
Not it! Damn it!
不是我  讨厌
Rachel, this is yours.
瑞秋  这是给你的
Why? What are these for?
为什么送我们这些礼物
You'll see.
过会你就知道了
All right, everybody open them.
好了  大家都请打开来看看吧
Wow, this is so beautiful!
好漂亮啊
These are the ones I was looking at in the store!
这个正是我上次在商店里相中的那一款
- I know. - Oh, I love this!
-我知道  -我喜欢这个
A meatball sub!
赛百味肉丸三明治
Thanks!
谢谢
Seriously, guys, what's going on?
说真的  到底怎么回事
What are these for?
为什么送我们这些礼物
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before...
我先前不知道该怎么跟你们说
- ...but we got the house. - Enjoy!
-但是  我们买到那房子了  -各位好好享受吧
What did they say?
他们刚才说什么